Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ayres & Fiege architectural drawings
1939-1970
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ayres & Fiege (Firm)
LSC.0115
726.0 Linear Feet (242 map folders and 1 box)
Ayres & Fiege was a prolific Los Angeles architectural firm founded in 1946 by Donald Ayres and Herbert F. Fiege. The collection consists of the firm's architectural drawings, plans, and specifications from school, church, commercial and residential projects.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mrs. Donald Ayres, care of Sally Fuller, 1996.
The archives of Ayres & Fiege were stored at Donald Ayres' home in Encino, California. Following his death, the drawings were donated by his widow, in the care of neighbor Sally Fuller, to the UCLA Art Library's Special Collections. Responsibility for the materials was transferred to the Young Research Library's Department of Special Collections in 2001, where they were later processed.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9951842923606533
Biography
Donald Ayres (1904-) was born in Wilton Junction, Iowa and received his Bachelors and Masters degrees from the University of Illinois. He was a fellow of the Ecole de Beaux Arts in Paris in 1932, and a Carnegie scholar at Harvard University during the summers of 1935 and 1936. In 1946 he founded the architectural firm of Ayres & Fiege with his business partner, Herbert F. Fiege. The firm designed many buildings for the Archdiocese of Los Angeles, in addition to a large number of public and private schools, commercial buildings, and residential developments in the San Fernando Valley and Los Angeles metropolitan area. Their residential work included apartment complexes, private homes, additions and renovations to existing structures, and model and tract home designs for developers and private clients.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of original architectural drawings and specifications for approximately 700 projects designed by Ayres & Fiege. Additional materials include perspectives, sketches, duplicates of original drawings, bid records and standard materials forms.
The collection documents the popularization of mainstream architectural modernism during California's postwar period. The residential series illustrates paticularly well the patterns and tastes that informed the urbanization of Los Angeles during the 1950s and 1960s.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Educational facilities, 1947-1967 (21 map folders).
Parochial buildings, 1951-1968 (30 map folders).
Commercial buildings, 1945-1969 (26 map folders).
Clubs, 1963 (2 map folders).
Residential projects, 1939-1970 (163 map folders), subseries A-D as follows:
Apartments, 1945-1970 (30 map folders).
Private homes, 1939-1970 (73 map folders).
Additions and renovations, 1939-1968 (30 map folders).
Model and tract homes, 1947-1964 (30 folders).
Bids and forms, ca. 1940-1960 (1 box).
Architecture -- California -- San Fernando Valley -- Designs and plans.; Architecture -- California -- Los Angeles -- Designs and plans.; Architectural firms -- California, Southern -- Archives.; Ayres & Fiege (Firm)--Archives; Fiege, Herbert F.
- Series 1: Educational facilities., 1947-1967
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes designs commissioned by the Archdiocese of Los Angeles.
  - Childs Garden School--alterations and additions., 1947.; 2 items. (Folder 1)
    Job Number 618. Childs Garden School
    6251 Kester Ave. Van Nuys, CA. Original document: legal description and plot plan.
    Owner: Darrel Condley & Mercedes La Gasse.
  - St. Jane Francis de Chantel--school and school addition., 1951-1953.; 17 items. (Folder 2)
    Job Numbers 217-A, 53-4. St. Jane Francis de Chantel
    12940 Hamlin St. North Hollywood, CA.
    Set of original drawings: plans, sections, elevations and details.
    (Drafted by Laurence D. Voile, Civil Engineer).
    Owner: Catholic Church. Archdiocese of Los Angeles Calif.).
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--8 classroom school building., 1952.; 6 items. (Folder 3)
    General note
    See also Map folders 6, 25, 28, 31 36, 37, 48.
    Job Number 266. Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    Passon Blvd. Rivera, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations and details.
    Owner: Catholic Church. Archdiocese of Los Angeles (Calif.).
  - Salvail Valley School--8 classroom school building., 1953.; 10 items. (Folder 4)
    Job Number 53-13. Salvail Valley School
    13640 Sherman Way, Van Nuys, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, elevations, details and perspectives.
    Specifications.
    Owner: Mrs. Merle Salvail.
  - Fullbright Avenue School., 1953-1954.; 76 items. (Folder 5)
    Job Number 53-16. Fullbright Avenue School
    Fullbright Ave, Canoga Park, CA.
    Set of original (trace) drawings: architectural, structural, plumbing & heating and electrical, perspectives.
    Owner: Los Angeles School Board.
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--9 classroom school building., 1955.; 16 items. (Folder 6)
    See also Map folders 4, 25, 28, 31, 36, 37, 48.
    Job Number 55-10. Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    Set of original drawings for school building: architectural, structural, and electrical.
    Original parish drawings: plans, elevation, section and detail.
  - Guardian Angel School., 1955.; 13 items. (Folder 7)
    See also Map folder 30.
    Job Number 55-16. Guardian Angel School
    10880 Lehigh Ave. Pacoima, CA.
    Set of original drawings: architectural, mechanical and electrical.
    Church remodel document (1959).
  - Our Lady of Victory School., 1956.; 8 items. (Folder 8)
    See also Map folder 33.
    Job Number 56-5. Our Lady of Victory School
    50 Fetterly St. Los Angeles, CA.
    Set of original drawings: plans, sections, elevations, details.
  - Vaughn Street School., 1956-1957.; 57 items. (Folder 9)
    See also Map folder 20.
    Job Number 56-19. Vaughn Street School
    Vaughn St., Pacoima, CA.
    Set of original drawings: architectural, structural, civil, plumbing, mechanical and electrical.
    Elementary School Standards.
  - St. Brigid Elementary School., 1959.; 23 items. (Folder 10)
    See also Map folder 23.
    Job Number 59-34. St. Brigid Elementary School
    52nd St. Los Angeles, CA.
    Set of original drawings: architectural, structural, and electrical.
    Sign Detail.
  - St. Ferdinand School & assembly hall., 1959-1960.; ca. 50 items. (Folder 11)
    See also Map folder 26.
    Job Numbers 59-38, 60-6. St. Ferdinand School & assembly hall
    Coronel St. San Fernando, CA.
  - California Educational Clinic School., 1960.; 5 items. (Folder 12)
    Job Number 60-27. California Educational Clinic School
    15321 Magnolia Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
    Original Drawings and copies: master plan for the clinic campus, plans and elevations.
    Owner: California Educational Clinic.
  - Dearborn Street School (1 of 4)., 1961-1962.; 13 items. (Folder 13)
    Job Number 61-34. Dearborn Street School
    Dearborn St. Northridge, CA. Preliminary specifications prepared for the board of education. Preliminary drawings set. Owner: Los Angeles School Board.
  - Dearborn Street School (2 of 4)., 1961-1962.; 28 items. (Folder 14)
    Dearborn St. Northridge, CA.
    Incomplete set of original drawings: architectural, structural, heating and ventilation, plumbing, mechanical and electrical.
    Color selections.
  - Dearborn Street School (3 of 4)., 1961-1962.; 88 items. (Folder 15)
    Copy of set copy drawings: architectural, structural, heating and ventilation, plumbing, mechanical and electrical.
  - Dearborn Street School (4 of 4)., 1961-1962.; 11 items. (Folder 16)
    Copy of set drawings approved by King, Benioff & Associates, consulting engineers.
  - St. Matthias Girls High School--addition., 1961.; 30 items. (Folder 17)
    Job Number 61-47. St. Matthias Girls High School
    Huntington Park, CA.
    Set of original drawings: architectural, structural and electrical.
  - Mr. Charles Mureau School., 1962.; 10 items. (Folder 18)
    Job Number 62-15. Mr. Charles Mureau School
    Calabasas, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, sections and details for a two classroom school building, studio for Mr. Mureau and additions to manor house.
    Owner: Mr. Charles Mureau.
  - Our Lady of Perpetual Help--4 classroom school., 1964.; 15 items. (Folder 19)
    See also Map folders 39, 41, 51.
    Job Number 64-4. Our Lady of Perpetual Help
    Lyons Ave. Newhall, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations, details.
  - Vaughn St. School--additional facilities., 1964.; ca. 80 items. (Folder 20)
    See also Map folder 10.
    Job Number 64-18. Vaughn St. School
    Vaughn St. San Frenando (Pacoima), CA.
    Set of original drawings + 1 scaled copy: architectural, structural, civil, plumbing, mechanical and electrical.
  - Parmlee Avenue School., 1967.; ca. 110 items. (Folder 21)
    Job Number 67-9. Parmlee Avenue School
    Parmlee Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
    Set of original drawings + 1 scaled copy of classroom building and kitchen addition: architectural, structural, civil, plumbing, mechanical and electrical.
    Color selections, perspectives, millwork and cabinet details.
- Series 2: Parochial buildings., 1951-1968
  This series includes designs commissioned by the Archdiocese of Los Angeles. Includes drawings by Laurence D. Voile.
  - Churches--miscellaneous., no date.; Sketches on trace. (Folder 22)
  - Convents and Sisters Homes--miscellaneous., no date.; Sketches and preliminary drawings. (Folder 23)
  - Little Brown Church--addition., no date.; 1 item. (Folder 24)
    Addition for Little Brown Church
    4418 Coldwater Canyon Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
    Elevation, plan.
    Section and foundation plan.
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--church building., 1951.; 19 items. (Folder 25)
    See also Map folders 3, 6, 28, 31, 36, 37, 48.
    Job Number 227. Church for the parish of Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    5 photographs of the church dated 1951-52.
  - St. Ferdinand Parish--rectory and convent., 1953-1954.; 36 items. (Folder 26)
    See also Map Folder 11.
    Job Numbers 53-6, 54-2c. Rectory and convent for St. Ferdinand Parish
    San Fernando, CA.
    (Drafted under the title of Laurence D. Voile, Civil Engineer).
  - Immaculate Heart Parish--church and retreat house ("Casa de Maria")., 1950-1954.; ca. 40 items. (Folder 27)
    Job Number 53-21. Chapel unit "Cases de Maria" for Immaculate Heart Parish
    Montecito, CA.
    Original drawings for guest cottages and chapel: plans, sections, elevations, details, schedule.
    Original and copies of internal and external perspectives on trace.
    Details for fixtures on trace, (1953-1954).
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--sister's residence & parish garage., 1954-1955.; 16 items. (Folder 28)
    See also Map folders 3, 6, 25, 31, 36, 37, 48.
    Job Numbers 54-48, 55-9. Sister's residence and parish garage for Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    Structural notes.
  - St. Jane Francis--addition to sister's residence., 1954-1955.; 11 items. (Folder 29)
    See also Map folder 7.
    Job Numbers 54-53, 55-57, 55-77. Additions to sister's residence for St. Jane Francis
    Victory Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations.
    Details.
    Garage relocation plan.
  - Guardian Angel Parish--sister's residence., 1955.; 10 items. (Folder 30)
    Job Number 55-15. Sister's residence for Guardian Angel Parish
    Pacoima, CA.
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--church alterations., 1955.; 5 items. (Folder 31)
    See also Map folders 3, 6, 25, 28, 36, 37, 48.
    Job Number 55-49. Church alterations for Santa Maria Anna de Parades
  - Mary Immaculate Parish--sister's residence., 1955-1956.; 8 items. (Folder 32)
    Job Number 55-43. Sister's residence for Mary Immaculate Parish
    10264 Rincon, Pacoima, CA.
    Original architectural drawings: plans, sections, elevations, details.
  - Sisters of Our Lady of Victory--sister's residence., 1955-1956.; 12 items. (Folder 33)
    See also Map folder 8.
    Job Number 55-70. Sister's residence for Sisters of Our Lady of Victory
    Belvedere, CA.
  - Holy Family Parish--rectory., 1956.; 12 items. (Folder 34)
    See also Map folder 42.
    Job Number 56-41. Rectory for the Holy Family Parish
    1220 Stanford Ave. Wilmington, CA.
    Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations, details, perspective.
  - St. Aloysius Parish--sister's residence., 1957.; 21 items. (Folder 35)
    See also Map folder 44.
    Job Number 57-30. Sister's residence for St. Aloysius Parish
    Nadeau St. Los Angeles CA.
    Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations, details, perspectives.
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--auditorium., 1957.; 10 items. (Folder 36)
    See also Map folders 3, 6, 25, 28, 31 37, 48.
    Job Number 57-41. Auditorium for Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    Set of original drawings: architectural and structural.
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--parish rectory., 1958.; 10 items. (Folder 37)
    See also Map folders 3, 6, 25, 28, 31, 36, 48.
    Job Number 58-35. Parish rectory for Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    Set of original drawings: architectural, electrical.
  - St. Margaret Mary Alacaque--rectory and convent., 1959.; 28 items. (Folder 38)
    See also Map folder 47.
    Job Number 59-2. St. Margaret Mary Alacaque
    2030 W. 255th St. Lomita, CA.
    Set of original drawings: architectural, electrical and heating.
    Original perspectives.
  - Our Lady of Perpetual Help--church hall, school and church alterations., 1960.; 46 items. (Folder 39)
    See also Map folders 19, 41, 51.
    Job Number 60-14. Our Lady of Perpetual Help (multiple projects)
    Set of original drawings: architectural, structural, electrical.
    Color Schedule.
  - First Methodist Church--addition., 1961-1963.; 12 items. (Folder 40)
    Job Number 61-41. Additions for the First Methodist Church
    6412 Rita Ave. Huntington Park, CA.
    Initial proposal.
    Case work drawings.
    Original plans (1921) by Rea and Garstang Architects.
  - Our Lady of Perpetual Help--rectory., 1962.; 13 items. (Folder 41)
    See also Map folders 19, 39, 51.
    Job Number 62-8. Rectory for Our Lady of Perpetual Help
    23233 Lyons Ave. Newhall, CA.
    Surveyors map.
  - Holy Family Parish--hall., 1963-1964.; 10 items. (Folder 42)
    See also Map folder 34.
    Job Number 63-32. Hall for Holy Family Parish
  - Beatitudes of Our Lord Parish--church and school., 1964-1966.; ca. 60 items. (Folder 43)
    Job Number 64-22. Beatitudes and master plot for Our Lord Parish
    Santa Gertrudes Ave. La Mirada, Orange county, CA.
    Preliminary original drawings: plot plan, plans, elevations, sections.
    Complete set of original drawings: architectural, electrical, civil and details.
    Duplicate copy of electrical drawings.
  - St. Aloysius Parish--rectory., 1966.; 7 items. (Folder 44)
    See also Map folder 35.
    Job Number 66-3. Rectory for St. Aloysius Parish
    Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations, colored elevation, details.
  - St. Ann Parish--hall., 1966.; 14 items. (Folder 45)
    Job Number 66-5. St. Ann hall
    340 Tenth St. Seal Beach, CA.
    Copy of Surveyor's map.
    Copy of Engineer's notes.
  - St. Rose of Lima--rectory., 1966.; 43 items. (Folder 46)
    Job Number 66-6. St. Rose of Lima
    Royal Ave. Simi, CA.
    Original architectural drawings and copies of drawings: plans, sections, elevations, colored elevation, details.
    Demolition plan.
  - St. Margaret Mary Alacaque--assembly hall., 1966- 1968.; 6 items. (Folder 47)
    See also Map folder 38.
    Job Numbers 66-20, 68-11. Assembly building for St. Margaret Mary Alacaque
    Set of original drawing: architectural, civil, mechanical and electrical.
    Original perspective.
    Plan and sections for equipment shed.
  - Santa Maria Anna de Parades--church remodel., 1967.; 19 items. (Folder 48)
    See also Map folders 3, 6, 25, 28, 31, 36.
    Job Number 67-13. Remodel existing church for Santa Maria Anna de Parades
    Original drawings: plans and details.
    Original perspective and copy.
  - Mary Immaculate Parish--shade pavillion and assembly building., 1967-1969.; 5 items. (Folder 49)
    Job Number 67-25. Shade pavilion and assembly building for Mary Immaculate Parish
    13838 Mercer St. Pacoima, CA.
    Preliminary plans.
    Tract documents.
    Surveyors plan.
    Original drawings for assembly building and shade pavilion: plans, details, schedule.
  - The Little White Chapel Church--alterations and additions., 1968.; 3 items. (Folder 50)
    Job Number 68-19. Alterations and additions for the Little White Chapel Church
    1711 North Ayon St. Burbank, CA.
    Original drawing: plans and sections.
    Copy of original drawing.
    Initial correspondence.
    Owner: Samual McLean.
  - Our Lady of Perpetual Help--library., 1968.; 6 items. (Folder 51)
    See also Map folders 19, 39, 41.
    Job Number 68-22. Library and office building for Our Lady of Perpetual Help
    Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections, details.
    Owner: Catholic Church.
    Archdiocese of Los Angeles (Calif.).
- Series 3: Commercial buildings., 1945-1969
  This series includes designs for stores, restaurants, nurseries, car dealerships, motels, and medical and brokerage offices.
  - Miscellaneous., no date.; 18 items. (Folder 52)
    Original and copies of perspectives and plans on trace paper. Prototypes for hotels, restaurants, swimming pools, civic center. Undated perspectives of the Encino chamber of commerce, O'Halloran Electronic Sales, Patio Corner shopping center.
  - ., 1945 (Folder 53)
    - Einzig Lawyers Office & Apartment., 1945?; 1.; 3 items.
      Einzig Lawyers Office & Apartment
      626 North Robertson, Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawings: plan, section, interior, exterior elevation and details.
      Owner: Ben Einzig.
    - Barsby Store Building., 1945?; 2.; 1 item.
      Barsby Store Building--remodel
      4358 Laurel Canyon Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: elevation, plan and details.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Barsby.
    - Tooper Motel., 1945.; 3.; 1 item.
      Tooper Motel--addition
      11733 Ventura Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: elevation, plan, section and details.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Geo. R. Bliss.
    - Geo Bliss Sky Haven., 1945?; 4.; 2 items.
      Geo Bliss Sky Haven--lodge alterations
      Original drawings: plan, interior elevations and details.
  - ., 1946 (Folder 54)
    - Needleman Fashion Bootery., 1946.; 1.; 1 item.
      Needleman Fashion Bootery--remodel
      Original drawing: elevations, plan, sections and details.
    - Dr. Babior Medical Building., 1946.; 2.; 6 items.
      Job Number 481. Dr. Babior Medical Building
      Sunland Blvd. Roscoe, CA.
      Original drawings: exterior and interior elevations, plans, section and details.
      Drawings by S.S. White Dental Mfg. Company.
      Owner: Dr. Louis S. Baboir.
    - Leon Restaurant and Store Building., 1946.; 3.; 4 items.
      See also Map folder 55, items 6 and 7.
      Job Number 482. Leon Restaurant and Store Building
      4439 Sunset Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original Drawings: elevations, plans, section and details.
      Owner: Mr. Albert Leon.
    - Gillson Grocery Store (Ventura Ranch Market)., 1946.; 4.; 2 items.
      Job Number 508. Gillson Grocery Store (Ventura Ranch Market)--remodel
      13726 and 13730 Ventura Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
      Original Drawings: elevations, plans, sections and details.
      Owner: Mr. Lee Gillson.
    - Traub Store Building., 1946?; 5.; 1 item.
      Job Number 524. Traub Store Building
      529 S. Figueroa St. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing: elevations, plans, sections and details.
      Owner: Mr. S. Traub.
    - Stewart Restaurant and Store., 1946?; 6.; 2 items.
      Job Number 525. Stewart Restaurant and Store
      13809 Ventura Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
      Original drawing: elevations, plans and sections.
      Owner: Mr. J.M. Stewart.
    - Best Store and Utility Buildings., 1946.; 7.; 2 items.
      Job Number 529. Best Store and Utility Buildings
      11330 Ventura Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: elevations, plans, sections and details.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. William Best.
    - McLaughlin Theatre Building., 1946.; 8.; 2 items.
      Job Number 534. McLaughlin Theatre Building
      U.S. Highway #20, Lucerne, Lake County, CA.
      Owner: Mr. John S. McLaughlin.
    - Beatty Golf Shop., 1946?; 9.; 1 item.
      Job Number 545. Beatty Golf Shop
      Vermont St. Los Angeles, CA.
      Original drawing: elevations, plans and section.
      Owner: Mr. C. E. Beatty.
    - K & M Market., 1946.; 10.; 4 items.
      Job Number 547. K & M Market--alterations and additions
      18438 Ventura Blvd. Tarzana, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections and details.
      Owner: Chas E. Mead & P.J. Dornish.
  - ., 1947 (Folder 55)
    - Studio City Chamber of Commerce., 1947.; 1.; 1 item.
      Studio City Chamber of Commerce--festival layout
      Original drawing: proposed plot layout.
      Owner: Studio City Chamber of Commerce.
    - Norgaard Dog Kennel., 1947?; 2.; 1 item.
      Job Number 600. Norgaard Dog Kennel
      Owner: Mrs. Grace Norgaard.
    - Moore Store Building., 1947.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 601. Moore Store Building
      11669 Van Owen St. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawing: plans, elevations and section.
      Owner: J.R. "Dick" Moore.
    - Brassfield Store Building., 1947?; 4.; 1 item.
      Job Number 611. Brassfield Store Building
      So. East Cor. Ventura and Laurel Canyon Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevation, sections and details.
      Owner: Bloomfield Brothers.
    - Bloomfield Brothers Gas Station., 1947.; 5.; 4 items.
      Job Number 612. Bloomfield Brothers Gas Station
      8060 Lankershim Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevation and section.
      Owner: Mr. Carl Brassfield.
    - Leon Store Building., 1947.; 6.; 5 items.
      See also Map folder 54, item 3.
      Job Number 635. Leon Store Building--alterations and additions
      Original drawings: elevations, plans, section and details.
      Engineer's calculations.
    - Leon Store Building., 1947.; 7.; 2 items.
      Job Number 635-A. Leon Store Building--alterations and additions
    - Wendt Store Building., 1947.; 8.; 2 items.
      Job Number 640. Wendt Store Building
      3rd St. Montebello, CA.
      Original drawings: plans, elevations, section and details.
      Owner: Mr. & Mrs. G. H. Wendt.
    - Zerwer Store Building., 1947?; 9.; 2 items.
      Job Number 649. Zerwer Store Building
      7240 Woodley Ave.
      Owner: Mr. Zerwer.
  - ., 1948 (Folder 56)
    - Morey and Eaton Realtor., 1948.; 1.; 1 item.
      Morey and Eaton Realtor
    - Smith-Rowsey Nurseries., 1948.; 2.; 1 item.
      Smith-Rowsey Nurseries--flower shop
      4220 Coldwater Canyon Ave. Studio City, CA.
    - Bivins Wood Working Shop., 1948.; 3.; 1 item.
      Job Number 674. Bivins Wood Working Shop
      432 N. Moss St. Burbank, CA.
      Owner: T. R. Bivins.
    - Solomon Store Building., 1948.; 4.; 4 items.
      Job Number 712. Solomon Store Building
      5226-26 1/2-28 Laurel Canyon Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
      Owner: Edward Solomon.
    - Kover Restaurant Building., 1948.; 5.; 9 items.
      See folder 77, item 1.
      Job Number 713. Kover Restaurant Building-- additions
      14649 Ventura Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
      Original and Copies of drawings: plans, elevations, sections and details.
      Owner: Ed Kover.
    - Armstrong Market Building., 1948, 1950.; 6.; 16 items.